村越　打て～！
Shoot, Murakoshi!
Keep looking forward.
前だけ向いてろ
その上で プレーヤーとして　あがき続けろ
And above all else, continue developing as a player.
抜かったら容赦しない
I will not hold back if you break any of these conditions.
フン
「Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　ｗｅ　ｓｔａｎｄ，　Ｆｌｙ　ａ　ｆｌａｇ 風を受け止めて」
United we stand, Fly a flag!
kaze o uketomete
風を受け止めて
Let the wind blow through you
「Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　ｗｅ　ｓｔａｎｄ，　Ｆｌｙ　ａ　ｆｌａｇ たなびけ勝利のｆｌａｇ」
United we stand, Fly a flag!
tanabike shouri no flag
たなびけ勝利の flag
Let the victory flag trail in the wind
「遥かなゴールを信じて 走り続けて」
haruka na gooru o shinjite
遥かなゴールを信じて
Believe in the goal that lies in wait and keep running
hashiri tsuzuketeke
走り続けてけ
hibi yume tsumugu monotachi e furisosoge hikari yo
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ降り注げ光よ
Let light pour down upon the weaver of dreams
「日々夢紡ぐ者達へ 降り注げ光よ」
「汗は裏切らないって 唇噛み締め」
ase wa uragiranaitte kuchibiru kamishime
汗は裏切らないって唇噛み締め
Your sweat won't betray you, so bite down on your lips
「何度も立ち上がり 大地を駆け抜ける」
nandomo tachiagari daichi o kakenukeru
何度も立ち上がり大地を駆け抜ける
And stand back up again and again as you dash across the earth
「夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ」
yume ni owari wa naitte me o kagayakase
夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ
Our dreams never end, so keep on shining
「Ｌｅｔ’ｓ　ｓｔａｒｔ　ｎｏｗ ＧＩＡＮＴ　ＫＩＬＬＩＮＧ」
Let's start now GIANT KILLING!
「ｆｏｒ　ｔｈｅ　ｒｉｇｈｔ ｈｏｌｄ　ｏｎ　ｔｉｇｈｔ」
For the right! Hold on tight!
「ｍｙ　ｓｔｏｒｙ…」
My story...
「ｆｏｒｅｖｅｒ」
Forever...
カ…　カンファレンス？
C-Conference?
It's the League Press Conference!
リーグ　プレス　カンファレンスよ！ 全チームの監督が勢ぞろいして
All managers from the league will come together and promote their teams to the media.
スポーツ誌とか　テレビのプレス向けに 自分のチームをアピールすんの
Nah, I'm not cut out for this stuff.
いいよ　俺そういうの
あっ！　なに寝てんのよ！
Why are you going back to sleep?!
早く支度して！　もう出るわよ！
Get yourself prepared, quick!
We're heading off!
遅れて　すみません
Sorry for the wait!
遅いぞ　お前たち！　達海は 正装で来させろと言っただろ
You guys are slow!
Didn't I tell you to get Tatsumi to dress formally for the event?
そう言ったんだけど…  いいんだよ
I did tell him, but...
It's alright! The enemies' bosses will be swarming this place, right?
敵が　ワンサカ来てんだろ？ だったら　ここも戦場じゃんか
Then, this place is going to be a battlefield, meaning that we have to come in our battle suits.
戦闘服で臨まねえと
It's all about our spirit.
気合いだよ　気合い
な　村越
Isn't that right, Murakoshi?
気合い入ってるな　キャプテン
The captain looks really smart.
村越　随分とイカした格好 してるじゃないか
You're dressed really well today, Murakoshi.
うん？　…あんた！
You are...
あっ！ あ　…不破
Fuwa...
ごぶさたしてます　永田会長  またお会いできてうれしいですよ
Long time no see, Chairman Nagata.
It's a pleasure to be able to meet you again.
名古屋の新監督だそうだな  ウチの時みたいな
I heard you're now the new manager of Nagoya.
Be careful there; don't make the same mistakes you made during your reign on our team.
失敗はしないよう 気を付けることだな
フフ　相変わらず 責任転嫁がお上手だ
I see you're still the same, shirking your own responsibilities.
フロントがきちんとしてないと いくら監督や選手が優秀でも
No matter how outstanding the manager and his players are...
Their efforts will go to waste if the Board of Directors is not doing its part of the job.
泣きを見ますよ
き…　貴様
Y-You bastard.
お？…　やあ　達海君
A pleasure to meet you, Tatsumi.
大変かもしれないけど 頑張って
It's going to be a tough job. Do your best.
I'm off then.
誰？　あれ  名古屋グランパレスの　不破監督だ
Who's that guy?
Fuwa of Nagoya Grand Palace.
過去に　ウチの監督を してた事がある
He was previously the manager of our club.
フロントとの確執が 絶えなくてな
He was playing hard ball with the Board of Directors during his reign here...
挙句の果てに　ウチを２部に 降格させちまったんだよ
And we ultimately got relegated to the second division.
ふ～ん
それでは　１部　全チーム 選手代表の入場です
And now, let's welcome our Division One's player representatives to our media conference!
リーグジャパン１部　全１８クラブを代表する 選手がそろいました
Japan League Division One. The player representatives of all 18 teams.
何か　いい顔してるな 村越のヤツ
That Murakoshi's holding up his expression really well.
え～？　私には ますます怖く見えるけど
But I think he looks very intimidating.
It's my honor to be able to play on the same pitch with you.
I wish the best of luck for both of us.
Thank you. May we have a good match.
Japanese managers are all so polite.
It will be nice to have a coach that can show a sense of hostility, though...
It can't be helped.
Osaka Gunners, the runner-up for the previous season, scored the most goals.
The leader of their team won't even be able to do so,
Even if he is going up face-to-face with you.
So Tatsumi became a manager here?
あの達海が監督かぁ  帰ってきたんなら
Why haven't you contacted us since you came back?
連絡ぐらいしろよ
達海監督  私　大阪ガンナーズの通訳の　園田です
Tatsumi...
I am the translator for Osaka Gunners, Sonoda.
そして　こちらが…
And this person here is...
I am Dulfer, the manager. My best wishes to you.
ああ　どうもどうも  よろしくね
Hi there! Pleased to meet you.
To all managers, it's about time to make your appearance.
監督の皆さん　そろそろ出番です  準備をお願いします
Please prepare yourselves!
Sonoda...
Yes?
He is going to be one hell of a manager.
それでは　昨年度 リーグチャンピオン　そして　天宮杯王者
And so, can we have the defending champion, as well as the Palace Cup winner,
Tokyo Victory's manager, Hirazuimi,
東京ヴィクトリー　平泉監督 　今シーズンへの 意気込みをお願いします
to talk about his expectations for the season ahead.
え～　我々は昨シーズン…
During the previous season, we...
次は達海さんだ 　心配だなぁ
The next one will be Tatsumi, I'm kinda worried.
大丈夫だって  問題発言だけはしないだろ
It'll be alright. I don't think he will do anything foolish.
Our aim is to...
リーグタイトル　ジャパンカップ　天宮杯　すべての タイトル独占を狙いにいきます
Win the league, the Japan Cup, as well as the Palace Cup.
A very ambitious goal from the champions! Thank you for your time.
力強い優勝宣言　ありがとう ございました 　続きまして
帰ってきたＥＴＵの星　監督としての 手腕が注目されます
The next person will be the returning Star of ETU...
All eyes will be on his managerial abilities this season,
イースト東京ユナイテッド 達海　猛監督　どうぞ！
East Tokyo United's Tatsumi Takeshi, take it away.
なに？　しゃべっていいの？
What's that? It's my turn already?
もう　しっかりしろよ～
Hey, calm down for a bit!
何か適当に書いといてよ  オーラがすごかったとか
You guys should be writing something more appropriate. For example, the team's high morale or something.
俺　監督始めて まだ４～５年でさぁ
Well, I've only been a manager for four or five years...
ＥＴＵは去年１５位でしょ  厳しいよね 　勝てっかなぁ
And ETU was only placed 15th last season...
That's a bit too lousy.
Can we win it?
That's good, every one of you will be writing us off...
ああよかった 　負けて当然と 思われてる…　って事は
Which means, for us, this will be the ideal situation to be in.
ウチにとっちゃ最高の環境だ  だって　ここにいる監督たち
For the other managers standing here, they will be the ones under pressure to win when they face us.
ウチとやる時　プレッシャーかかるよ  もし　負けでもしたら　赤っ恥だ
If they were to lose to us,
It would be a huge embarrassment.
その点ウチは失うものは何もない  のびのびと
We, on the other hand, have nothing to lose.
We will always be in our best condition.
ベストコンディションで臨める  へっ
ＥＴＵみたいな貧乏な弱小クラブが すげえフットボールして
Therefore, for a small and weak club such as ETU, we'll be playing at a higher standard.
We will then beat these so-called 'big teams' to a pulp. Wouldn't that feel good?
強豪クラブをバッタバッタとなぎ倒す  どうだ　痛快だろ
Just wait and see. I will transform the league of this nation into a very exciting one.
ま　見てなって 　この国のサッカー界 俺が面白くしてやるよ
以上！
That's all.
確かに プレシーズンマッチでの戦いぶり
From what I can see from the pre-season game, ETU should definitely not be underestimated.
ＥＴＵは　あなどれない  しかし　この世界
Still, you should not naively look down upon this world and do whatever you want, Tatsumi.
なめてかかってくれるほど 甘くはないよ　達海監督
Interesting.
う…　なんて事を  ビッグマウスにも程がある
How did this happen? He pushed the limit with his arrogant speech.
有里ちゃん 大丈夫かい？
Are you okay, Yuri?
Mr. Tatsumi?
ミスター　タツミ
I would like to have a word with you. Would you join me for lunch?
Who are you?
I am a football manager, just like you.
Do you like Fish & Chips?
I am a Frenchman, but I used to manage a team in England.
Back then, I had it almost every day.
I know a place nearby, where they serve good and cheap Fish & Chips.
Let's go.
That's weird, where did Tatsumi go?
あれ？　達海さん どこ行っちゃったのかしら
あっ！　もしかして　逃げた
Don't tell me... he ran off?
おっさんさぁ　監督って 言ってたけど　どこのチーム？
Hey old man, you said you are a manager, so which team are you managing?
顔を見た覚えが あるんだけどさぁ
You look familiar somehow.
Monsieur Tatsumi...
Listen.
I don't want you to panic or anything,
But I think,
We are lost.
我々って…　おっさんが 勝手に迷ったんじゃん
We're lost?!
And you were the one told me to follow you, right?
はい　俺のお勧めランチセット
Here, my recommended lunch set.
It looks like, I've put you through a lot of trouble...
For nothing, dear me.
いいよ　いいよ 　逆に 面倒くさい事　サボれたし
It's fine. Besides, I get to escape from that troublesome conference.
あ？　…お～
Go!
The ball's there!
Which side do you think will win?
The blue team.
But they're behind.
They will turn the game around soon.
だって　あいつらのほうが 一生懸命　走ってるし
Because they are running more emphatically than the red team.
声もよく出てる
What's more, they look more spirited. These kind of players are tough to beat.
That's true for the pros as well.
Is that the kind of football you're aiming for?
If so, we share the same view.
You know, they should have opened up the side a little more..
こっちは　ボワ～っとなって あっちが　ベロンとなれば
They should have do it just like this here, and do it just like that there.
ウイウイ！　ボワ～　ベロン  それでフニャドン
Yeah, yeah! Just like this and that!
Also, don't forget this!
もう　どこにいるのよ  遠くには行ってないと思うけど
Where did he run off to? He shouldn't have gone far...
あ～っ！　あいつ！
There you are!
あ…　あれって？
Hey, that guy's...
フニャドン　ドンドン　ズビズビ！ ハハハハ
心の声　ゲ～ッ！　あのフランス人 日本代表チームの　ブラン監督
He's that French guy!
Japan National Team's manager, Blanc?!
何なの？　何であんな人と 一緒にいるの？
What is this? Why is he together with him?
それも　あんなに楽しそうに 話してる 　まるで友達みたいに
And they are happily chatting away.
As if they are friends...
ピ　ピ～  やった～！
We won!
Good luck with your season.
I'm sure you'll put together a fine team.
I won't know that until I've tried it.
Of course you can!
You have the luck!
運ねぇ…　ま　そうかもね
Luck, huh?
I think so.
Besides, I have yet to pay my debt back to the footballing god.
俺　フットボールの神様に でかい貸しがあるし
いた～っ！
I found you!
I've been searching for you, Monsieur Blanc.
I'm sorry.
Didn't I tell you that you'll be having dinner with the people of the Association?
Ahh, yes.
ハハッ　怒られてら  駄目だぜ　おっさん
You got caught!
That's not good, old man.
大人が 怒られるような事しちゃ
How can you do such a thing?
ふ～ん　そうなんだ  そういう事　言えちゃうんだ
That's right!
So you know that too!
アハ…　アハ…　アハハハハ
The next time we meet, we'll have Fish & Chips!
うん　またね
Later.
Monsieur Blanc, you're putting us in a tight spot with your actions.
Please know your limits, sir. The whole of Japan is putting their hopes on you.
Cheer up a little bit.
What?
Today's little incident will have a great positive impact to the Japanese National Team.
よ～し！ 全部覚えた 　来い！
Alright! I've remembered them all!
Come on!
ええと　じゃあね ２番　黒田は既婚？　未婚？
Is the No.2 Kuroda single, or married?
Single.
未婚 ピンポーン！　じゃ １０番　ジーノの愛車は？
Correct! Then, what is Gino's favorite car?
Time's up!
ブッブー！　時間切れ
あ～　駄目だ　こんなんじゃ！ 開幕　明日なのに～！
No good. Tomorrow's the opening game!
絶対あるって  ＥＴＵから日本代表選手の招集
The Japan National Team will definitely pick out players from ETU!
有里ちゃん　この間から そればっかり言ってるなぁ
Yuri, you've been repeating that several times.
That's because I saw Tatsumi and Manager Blanc chatting away happily!
だって　達海さんとブラン監督　本当に 楽しそうにしゃべってたんだから
Well, the two of them are weird. They should click right away.
確かに変わり者同士… 馬が合いそうだ
There will certainly be more surprises in store for the ETU.
きっとＥＴＵは　これからすごい事が たくさん起こるんだよ
そのためのシーズン開幕じゃん  私たちも　頑張ろうね！
That's why we have to make preparations for this season's opener! Let's do our best!
That's right.
Matsubara and the rest are still here?
松原さんたち まだ　いたんですか？
コーチ陣だけのミーティングっスよ  我々　一枚岩となって
The coaching staff had a meeting just now.
We've decided to come together to mould Tatsumi into an important figure of our team!
達海　猛を男にしようってね
よし！　戦の前の景気づけだ！ おう！
Alright! We're going to rile up the pre-match atmosphere!
And so, they are starting it off with their usual drinking sessions.
やっぱり飲みに行くんだ
Yuri, Tatsumi is still...
有里ちゃん　達海のヤツ　まだ…  うん
部屋に　こもりっぱなし  全然出てこない
He's still cooped up in his room... Is he planning to not come out?
Ok, a little bit more...
よし　もうちょっとだ  引きずるんじゃねえぞ
Don't drag our time.
いよいよ明日か  何とか間に合ってよかったぜ
Tomorrow's the day... We've made it.
With this, the season opener is going to be a riot.
こいつがありゃ ホームでの開幕戦　派手にいける
くう～！　今から燃えてきた！ どうすかね　羽田さん　今期のＥＴＵ
I'm already all psyched up!
What do you think of the ETU team this season, Haneda?
村越さんを　キャプテンから 外したり戻したり
Stripping Murakoshi of his captaincy initially, and then renominating him again...
はっきり言って　達海のやり方は 気に食わねえ
I'm not really satisfied with the way Tatsumi does things, to be honest.
Besides, he did abandon ETU in the past. I do not approve of Tatsumi's appointment...
ＥＴＵを一度　見捨てた男だ  俺たちは達海を認めねえ
だが　俺たちユナイテッドスカルズは ＥＴＵを勝たせるために存在する
But we are the United Skulls. We're formed to bring ETU victory.
We need to believe in our own powers.
俺たちの力を信じろ！ チームを強くするのはサポーターだ！
The ones that will strengthen the team up is us, the fans!
パッカく～ん　握手して！
Paoka, shake my hand!
Me too, me too!
俺も　俺も！　…あ？
男は無視かよ～！
Ignoring the guys, are you?!
隅田川スタジアム…　久しぶりに 来たけど　やっぱり狭いわね　ここ
Sumidagawa stadium... Though I haven't come for a long time,
This place is still so small and narrow.
あれ？　藤澤さん
Oh? Miss Fujii!
珍しいね　どうしたの？ 山井さん
This is a rare sight. What brings you here?
Mr Yamai.
今シーズンは　ＥＴＵを 追いかけようかと思って
I'm planning to be reporting exclusively on ETU for this season.
ＥＴＵ番の山井さんに　いろいろと ご教授願えたら助かります
It will be a great help if you are able to help me in the exclusive reports, since ETU's your specialty.
藤澤さんの頼みとあらば 何でも教えるよ
As long as it's for you, I'll do all I can to help.
やっぱり　フリーの記者には 東京ヴィクトリーは　きついよね
It is definitely not easy for freelance reporters like you to be able to get reports on Tokyo Victory.
あそこは　各紙のエース級が 記事書くもんねぇ
Besides, reports for the top teams are all written by top reporters from the press.
乗り換えて正解だよ  じゃ
The boss made the right choice of getting you for this job.
Later then.
心の声　日本のサッカー界を 面白くしてやるですって？
Transforming the league of this nation into an exciting one?
見せてもらおうじゃない 達海　猛
Show me what you've got then, Tatsumi Takeshi.
East Tokyo United
Players' Locker Room
うし！　…行くぞ
Let's go.
おっしゃ～　来た～！
Alright, they're out!
目ん玉かっぽじって とくと見やがれ～！　これが
Open your eyes wide and look over here!
These are the fans that will be going through thick and thin with you this season!
俺たちサポーターが シーズンを共に戦う証しだ～！
「おおお～　俺たちの 誇り　おおお～　イースト東京ユナイテッド」
わ～　やるじゃない　スカルズ！
What a great job from the Skulls!
This is going to make publicity stunts so much easier.
こりゃ広報としても 気合い入るわ！
フフ　大衆も盛り上がっちゃって  さながらイタリアの夏祭りだ
The fans are brimming with so much passion... it feels just like a rowdy summer vacation back in Italy.
何スか？　イタリアの夏祭りって
What exactly is this "summer vacation in Italy"?
うお～！　気合い十分！ 磐田なんぞ恐れるに足らず！
The atmosphere is huge! We're only playing against Iwata, there's nothing to fear!
無駄にうるさいよ　クロ
You're noisy, so stop wasting your breath, Kuro.
Tatsumi Takeshi.
達海　猛  東京ヴィクトリー戦と　プレスカンファレンス
During the friendly against Tokyo Victory as well as the media conference,
あの男は　私を一瞬　ゾクッとさせる 何かを持ってた
He possesses a certain quality that captures people's attention.
頼むわよ　私はあなたに 懸けたんだから
My hopes are on you. I'm putting my entire freelance career on your shoulders.
フリーライターとしての　この１年
相手は 昨シーズン６位の　ジャベリン磐田
The opponent today is Javelin Iwata, which finished 6th in the previous season.
チームを率いて１４年　倉茂監督の パスサッカーは　知的というより狡猾
Leading the team for fourteen years...
Kurashi has built up a team which emphasizes passing. He's sly rather than smart.
時の流れは早いもんだ  あの小僧が監督とはな
Time flies, doesn't it? The kid from before has now become a manager.
いつの話してんだよ　ジジイ  ボケるには　まだ早いだろ
And when exactly was that, old man? It's still too early for you to go senile, you know.
年寄りが増える時代だ  いたわる気持ちを大切にな
The society's getting older, learn to have some manners.
やなこった
I'm not really into that sort of thing.
心の声　ちぇ　倉茂のクソジジイめ
Tsk, that old hag.
I'd hoped to meet him much later...
当たるなら もうちょっと先がよかったぜ
I'm not letting you do what you did when you faced Tokyo Victory, Tatsumi.
東京ヴィクトリー戦の ようにはいかんぞ　達海
ワシは平泉君より　よっぽど ひねくれとるからのう 　フン
I am definitely a much more crafty opponent than Hirazumi.
ＥＴＵのキャプテンは 結局　村越
The captain of ETU is still Murakoshi.
ETU is still the same old squad.
ＥＴＵは何も変わっていない  そう思いたいヤツは思え
The majority still thinks of it that way.
俺たちは変わる！
However, we'll show them.
勝って　それを証明してやる！
We have to win and prove a point!
えい！
That was close!
惜しい！ 攻めろ～！
Continue the attack!
悪くねえ  先制点　いけるぜ！
Not bad! We should be able to score first!
心の声　のれてる 　東京ヴィクトリーと やり合った実力は　ウソじゃねえ！
It's for real. The quality we displayed previously against Tokyo Victory is for real.
すいません　王子  次こそ！
I'm sorry, Prince! I'll get it the next time!
頼むよ　セリー  せっかくいい流れなんだから
It's up to you, Sera. That was a great chance just now.
That's right, we can do it!
やれる！　やれるぞ！
何だよ　こいつら  飛ばしすぎだろ！
What's up with these guys? They're closing up so tightly!
へっ　クロスの名手 田辺が蹴り損なうとは
Even the dead ball specialist, Tanabe, is forced into making errors. The game is slowly turning in our favour.
完全にウチらのペース
「Ｙｏｕ’ｖｅ　ｇｏｔ　ｆｉｎｄ　ｔｈｅ　ｗａｙ　ｔｏ ｂｅｌｉｅｖｅ，　ｃａｒｒｙ　ｏｎ　ａｎｄ　ｃａｒｒｙ　ｏｎ」
You've got find the way to believe
Carry on and carry on
「Ｔｉｌｌ　ｙｏｕ　ｃａｎ　ｓｅｅ ｔｏｍｏｒｒｏｗ， Ｉ’ｌｌ　ｓａｙ　“ｎｅｖｅｒ　ｌｏｏｋ　ｂａｃｋ”」
Till you can see tomorrow
I'll say “never look back”
「追い風を待って そうｃｈａｎｃｅを のがすなら」
oikaze o matte
追い風を待って
Wait for the tailwind
sou chance o nogasunara
そう chance を逃すなら
And if you missed the chance
「自分が風になれ　ｎｏ　ｆｅａｒｓ， ｎｏ　ｔｅａｒｓ，　ｙｅｓ　Ｌｅｔ　ｉｔ　ｇｏ！」
jibun ga kaze ni nare
自分が風になれ
Become the wind yourself
No fears! No tears! Yes! Let it go!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｇｏｌｄ！） Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
We'll go!
genkai oikose yuke
限界追い越せ行け
Surpass your limits and go!
「限界追い越せ 行け　キツイほど ｈｅａｒｔ　ｉｎ　ｒｅｄ」
kitsui hodo heart in red
キツイほど　heart in red
The harder it is the redder your heart will be!
「Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！ （Ｓｔａｙ　ｃｏｏｌ！） Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Go on! Go on!
Stay cool!
We'll go!
「あすは 見えない　だから」
asu wa mienai dakara
あすは見えないだから
Because we can't see into the future
「Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｔｉｍｅ　ｔｏ　ｇｏ やめられない」
It's time to go yamerarenai
It's time to go やめられない
So it's time to go. We can't quit!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！ Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！　Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！」
Get tough!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｇｏｌｄ！） Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
We'll go!
「共に乗り越えて　行け 見えるか　Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｄａｙｂｒｅａｋ　ｔｈｅｒｅ」
tomo ni norikoete yuke
共に乗り越えて行け
Let's get through it together
mieruka It's daybreak there
見えるか It's daybreak there
Can you see that it's daybreak there?
「Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｃｏｏｌ！）　Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！ （Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）　予測できない」
Go on! Go on!
Stay cool!
We'll go!
yosoku dekinai dakara
予測できないだから
The future is unpredictable
「だから　Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｔｉｍｅ　ｔｏ　ｇｏ 止められない」
It's time to go tomerarenai
It's time to go 止められない
So it's time to go. We can't stop!
Pass it!
Quick!
Stop your aimless running, Tsubaki!
Stop joking, you bastard!
A competition?!